personalmba.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC

* * *

**Last updated:** November 9, 2018

## Services

The following websites (hereafter referred to as “Service” or “Services”) are owned and operated by Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC:

  * [personalmba.com](https://personalmba.com/), [book.personalmba.com](http://book.personalmba.com/), and [course.personalmba.com](http://course.personalmba.com/)

Please read this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”, “Policy”) carefully before using any of the Services operated by Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”). These terms apply to each of the Services listed above.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

## Definitions

### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

### Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

### User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

## Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Purchase information

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * _Session Cookies_. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * _Preference Cookies_. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * _Security Cookies_. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

You can find more information about our use of Cookies in our Cookies Policy.

## Use of Data

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.

Any such newsletter, marketing, or promotional email will only be sent after you confirm your consent to receive communications from us via clicking a confirmation link sent to your email address. (This process is typically referred to as “double opt-in,” and is used for all email marketing activities conducted by Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC.)

You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

## Retention of Data

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure Of Data

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Additional information about the security of User and Subscriber Personal Information is available in Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC’s Security Policy.

## Your Rights

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. In addition, please note that this is a manual process that may take up to 30 days to complete.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

#### Gauges

Gauges is a web analytics service that tracks and reports live and aggregate website traffic. Gauges uses the data collected to track, monitor, and report on the use of our Service.

Their privacy policy can be viewed at https://get.gaug.es/privacy

#### Momently

Momently is a web analytics service that tracks and reports aggregate website traffic. Momently uses the data collected to track, monitor, and report on the use of our Service.

Their privacy policy can be viewed at https://momently.com/privacy

#### Mixpanel

Mixpanel is provided by Mixpanel Inc.

You can prevent Mixpanel from using your information for analytics purposes by opting-out. To opt-out of Mixpanel service, please visit this page: https://mixpanel.com/optout/

For more information on what type of information Mixpanel collects, please visit the Terms of Use page of Mixpanel: https://mixpanel.com/terms/

### Email and Personalized Marketing

We may use third-party Service Providers to send you email communications required to operate the Service, or to send newsletters, marketing, promotional materials that you’ve requested from Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC.

In addition, we may use third-party Service Providers and/or Cookies to personalize our Services based on your purchases or web browsing behavior.

#### Podia

Podia is an online course delivery and email sending service that sends transactional, newsletter, marketing, and promotional emails related to our Services. In order to improve the quality of our Services, Podia may store information related to your purchase or web browsing behavior (“tags”) to personalize email content and ensure marketing and promotional emails are relevant to your interests.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.podia.com/privacy

#### Mailgun

Mailgun is an email sending service that sends transactional, newsletter, marketing, and promotional emails related to our Services.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.mailgun.com/privacy-policy

#### Postmark

Postmark is an email sending service that sends transactional emails related to our Services.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://wildbit.com/privacy-policy

#### ConvertKit

ConvertKit is an email sending service that sends transactional, newsletter, marketing, and promotional emails related to our Services. In order to improve the quality of our Services, ConvertKit may store information related to your purchase or web browsing behavior (“tags”) to personalize email content and ensure marketing and promotional emails are relevant to your interests.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://convertkit.com/privacy/

#### RightMessage

RightMessage is a website personalization service that we use to improve the quality of our Services and marketing by avoiding promotions that are superfluous or not relevant to your interests.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://rightmessage.com/privacy

### Customer Service

#### Spark

Spark is an email and customer service application that allows us to communicate with you via email and provide customer service.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://sparkmailapp.com/privacy

#### Front

Front is a customer service application that allows us to communicate with you via email and chat.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://frontapp.com/privacy-policy

#### Slack

Slack is a chat application that we use for internal communication, customer support, and to monitor activity in our Services.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://slack.com/privacy-policy

### Operations

We may use third-party Service Providers to operate our Services in a secure, reliable manner.

#### Heroku

Heroku, provided by Salesforce Inc, is the website and database hosting service we use to operate our Services.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/

#### Papertrail

Papertrail, provided by SolarWinds, is a log management service we use to detect and fix website errors.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.solarwinds.com/legal/privacy

#### Sentry

Sentry is an automated website error detection service we use to detect and fix website errors.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://sentry.io/privacy/

#### Skylight

Skylight, provided by Tilde Inc, is website and database monitoring service we use to detect and fix website errors.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.skylight.io/privacy

### Payments and Shipping

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

#### Stripe

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://stripe.com/us/privacy

#### Square

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://squareup.com/legal/privacy-no-account

#### PayPal

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

#### Blackbox

Blackbox is a shipping and logistics company that collects order and payment information through third-party payment processors like Stripe.

Additional information can be found at https://www.blackbox.cool

### Behavioral Remarketing

Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC may use remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

#### Amazon

Amazon is a retailer that sells a wide variety of goods and services, including Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC products.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496

#### Facebook and Instagram

Facebook and Instagram are social media services operated by Facebook, Inc.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy

#### Twitter

Twitter is a social media service operated by Twitter, Inc.

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at https://twitter.com/privacy

### “Do Not Track” Signals

Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”) for Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC cookies and information required to operate our Services.

Our third-party Service Providers may support Do Not Track (“DNT”), in accordance with their respective Privacy Policies.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Business Transfers

In the event Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC sells (in whole or in part) one or more of its Services, either individually or via an acquisition or merger with a third-party, Personal Data and Usage Data may be transferred to the acquiring third-party.

In using the Services, you acknowledge that such business transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC, its Services, or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact:

**Worldly Wisdom Ventures LLC**  
305 W. Magnolia St. #115  
Fort Collins, CO 80521

**Email:** inquiries@worldlywisdomventures.com  
**Phone:** +1-970-484-1512  
**Fax:** +1-970-329-2767 

* * *
